<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[1174]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[test]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[<strong>About The Event</strong>

Since 1927, the Ryder Cup has become one of the world’s greatest sporting events. Every two years, 24 of the best players from Europe and the United States go head-to-head in match play competition. Each of the first two days includes one four-match session of four-ball and one four-match session of foursomes. The final day is reserved for 12 singles matches.<strong> </strong>Drama, tension, incredible golf, camaraderie and sportsmanship are served in equal measure, captivating an audience of millions around the world.

<strong>Micro-Internships:</strong>

<strong>Sign-up and receive notification as new events and information is released.</strong>

Advance your career; learn transferable (soft) skills through our micro-learning program and apply for micro-internships at events like this.

Micro-internships may range from 1 to 14 days (perfect for busy schedules). Learners can apply for roles that are posted once they have completed fieldX101*

Sign up now! Start training, get notified and be ready when events are confirmed, and positions are posted.

fieldX micro-learning and micro-internships build your capability for any discipline. Sport, marketing, media, hospitality, nursing, computer science, criminal justice; anyone in any discipline who wants to power up their transferable skills and get work experience!

<strong>Training:</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>fieldX101 Lessons</li>
 	<li>Reopen Responsibly Lessons</li>
</ul>
<em>NOTE:
The safety and well-being of our fieldXers has been and always will be fieldXperience’s highest priority, especially during challenging times like these. We will provide updates, changes or cancellations as announced.</em>

<em>We strongly recommend following <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/community/large-events/considerations-for-events-gatherings.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>guidelines set by the CDC</strong></a></em>

<em>Learners can apply after receiving a score of 100% in prerequisite lessons</em>

<em>(lessons can be repeated to improve scores).</em>

<em>Micro-internships may range from 1 to 14 days (perfect for busy schedules).</em>

<em>Learners can apply for roles that are posted once they have completed fieldX101</em>]]></content>
		<excerpt><![CDATA[]]></excerpt>
		<date><![CDATA[2023-03-10]]></date>
		<posttype><![CDATA[tp_event]]></posttype>
		<permalink><![CDATA[https://www.challenge.fieldx.org/events/test/]]></permalink>
		<imageurl><![CDATA[]]></imageurl>
		<imagetitle><![CDATA[]]></imagetitle>
		<imagecaption><![CDATA[]]></imagecaption>
		<imagedescription><![CDATA[]]></imagedescription>
		<imagealttext><![CDATA[]]></imagealttext>
		<imagefeatured><![CDATA[]]></imagefeatured>
		<attachmenturl><![CDATA[]]></attachmenturl>
		<eventcategories><![CDATA[]]></eventcategories>
		<eventtags><![CDATA[]]></eventtags>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<authorid><![CDATA[4]]></authorid>
		<authorusername><![CDATA[admin-fieldx]]></authorusername>
		<authoremail><![CDATA[tan90degrees@gmail.com]]></authoremail>
		<authorfirstname><![CDATA[]]></authorfirstname>
		<authorlastname><![CDATA[]]></authorlastname>
		<slug><![CDATA[test]]></slug>
		<format><![CDATA[]]></format>
		<template><![CDATA[]]></template>
		<parent><![CDATA[0]]></parent>
		<parentslug><![CDATA[0]]></parentslug>
		<order><![CDATA[0]]></order>
		<commentstatus><![CDATA[closed]]></commentstatus>
		<pingstatus><![CDATA[closed]]></pingstatus>
		<postmodifieddate><![CDATA[2023-03-10]]></postmodifieddate>
	</node>
</data>
